rlfans.com 2018-11-04

# PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY POLICY
We have taken steps to ensure that any information provided to us through the use of our site is
safe and secure. The following applies to any information you provide to us, for example during any
registration process.
If you send us personal correspondence such as emails or letters, submissions through
http:/support.rlfans.com, post reviews or other messages on the bulletin boards of chat areas, then
we may collect this information into a file specific to you. All such information collected by us shall
be referred to as “Personal Information”.
You authorise us to use, store or otherwise process any Personal Information which relates to you
and identifies you, including but not limited to your name and address, to the extent reasonably
necessary to provide the services which are available through our site by us, our partners, successors
(including the purchase of the whole or part of our business). If you would like details of the
companies involved in our business these will be provided on request.
You must ensure that the Personal Information you provide is accurate and complete.
We reserve the right to store any information we have about you and disclose such information if
we determine that such disclosure is necessary, including but not limited to, in order to comply with
applicable law, or in connection with any action or investigation, or to enforce these Terms of Use.
We will not transfer, sell or licence any of your Personal Information to third parties for any reasons
other than those set out above.
All Personal Information is processed in accordance with the relevant data protection legislation of
England & Wales at the time.
By using our site you agree to the processing and disclosure of the Personal Information for the
purposes set out above. If you would like to review or modify any part of your Personal Information
then you should email us at paul.coward@rlfans.com.
